<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animal Lover</string>
    <string name="new_user_sign_here">New User?    <u>SIGN UP</u> Here</string>
    <string name="already_registered_login_here">Already Registered? <u>Login here</u> </string>
    <string name="doing_great_work">Help the Animals\n If you love them</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">This guide will help you setup\n everything about Animal Lover</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="typesfoodcat">
         1.Dry food diet\n
        2.Wet food diet\n
        3.Renal diet\n
        4.Gastrointestinal health diets\n
        5.High energy diet\n

    </string>
    <string name="typesmedicinecat">
         1.Fluids for Cats\n
        2.Digestive Disorder Products for Cats\n
        3.Hormone Replacement or Inhibition for Cats\n
        4.Heart and Blood Pressure Drugs for Cats\n
        5.Bronchodilators for Cats\n

    </string>
    <string name="foodlistcat">
          1.Salmon\n
         2.Trout\n
         3.Herring\n
         4.Mackerel\n
         5.Tuna\n
         6.Whitefish\n
         7.Chicken\n
         8.Turkey\n
         9.Pheasant\n
         10.Beef\n

    </string>
    <string name="typesfoodbird">
        #1: Bird seed mixtures\n
        #2: Bird cake and food bars\n
        #3: Live foods and other insect foods\n
        #4: Breed your own mealworms\n
        #5: Household scraps for birds
    </string>

    <string name="typesfooddog">
        #1: Kibble/Dry\n
        #2: Canned\n
        #3: Semi-Moist\n
        #4: Home Cooked\n
        #5: Raw
    </string>
    <string name="foodlistdog">
       Top Food Names for Female Dogs:\n
        1.Ginger\n
        2.Pepper\n
        3.Cookie
        4.Cinnamon
        5.Snickers\n\n
        Top Food Names for Male Dogs\n
        1.Pickles\n
        2.Peanut\n
        3.Pepper\n
        4.Brownie\n
        5.Chip\n
    </string>
    <string name="when_your_pet_has_a_medical_condition_your_veterinarian_might_prescribe_one_or_more_medications_intended_to_manage_treat_or_cure_the_problem_although_there_are_some_veterinary_specific_drugs_many_of_the_drugs_used_in_veterinary_medicine_are_the_same_as_those_used_in_people_ata_medicine_er_vitor_deoa_lagbe_jeta_already_medicines_doc_file_deoa_ache_amra_kono_vabe_daye_thakbo_na_jekono_kisu_medicine_use_korar_agee_doctor_or_prescribe_hoa_lagbe">When your pet has a medical condition, your veterinarian might prescribe one or more medications intended to manage, treat or cure the problem. Although there are some veterinary-specific drugs, many of the drugs used in veterinary medicine are the same as those used in people. ata medicine er vitor deoa lagbe jeta already medicines doc file deoa ache ... amra kono vabe daye thakbo na . jekono kisu medicine use korar agee doctor or prescribe hoa lagbe</string>
    <string name="warning"><b>Warning- </b>As with any fresh food you offer your bird, remove and discard any leftovers a
        couple of hours after serving. This prevents bacteria growth inside of your pet’s cage. Take it easy on the grapes,
        however. They contain a lot of sugar. </string>
    <string name="warning2">
        <b>Warning- </b>Remember to never serve raw beans to your companion bird as they can be toxic unless cooked.
    </string>
    <string name="dog_food">"Dogs are usually carnivorous and eat almost all types of food. But wild dogs eat the flesh, bones, various organs and digested plants of other animals that prey on themselves. Although dogs are carnivores, they consume very small amounts of vegetable food for prey digestion.
        \n\nFeed good quality dry food or canned food according to the age and weight of the dog. These processed foods contain the right amount of nutrients. Dog food of different brands and flavors is available in the market and in different online shops. However, look at the expiration date on the food packet and try to feed premium food.
        \n\n\t\t •\tFeed Natural Foods. Such as: meat (beef, chicken, sheep, etc.), eggs, bones and various vegetable foods.
        \n\n\t •\tIf your dog has a problem with his teeth or gums, do not let him eat the bones. Bone can cause various gum and dental diseases. Playing too much bone can cause constipation and the bone should be large so that the whole bone does not get into the mouth.
        \n\n\t •\tOccasionally canned fish such as sardines, tuna, salmon, etc. can be fed as a treat  •\tOccasionally a small amount of boiled vegetables such as sweet pumpkin, carrot, broccoli, etc. can be fed.  •\tDogs can be fed rice or pasta mixed with boiled meat (without spices, onions, garlic).
        \n\n\t•\tLet the dog eat grass which acts as a vegetable substitute and helps digestion. Beware of chemical and poisonous plants.
        \n\n\t•\tThe amount of food depends on the size, breed, age, weight, exercise, etc. of the dog. However, it should be noted that extra food or very small amount of food should not be fed.
        \n\n\t•\tAdult dogs need to be fed twice a day. Exercise and walking should not be done just before and just after eating.
        \n\n\t•\tSome foods that should not be fed to dogs (toxic to dogs) are onions, garlic, chocolate, coffee and caffeine, avocado fruit, raw flour, yeast, grapes, raisins, nuts, fruit seeds or grains such as mango flour, avocado fruit Grains, raw tomatoes, mushrooms, daily fish, small bones, Xylitol (used instead of sugar in various foods), chewing gum, toothpaste, etc. "
    </string>
    <string name="fish_food">"What you feed your fish and how much you feed them—is an important part of providing a healthy environment for them. There's much more to offering the proper diet for a fish than just sprinkling a few flakes on top of the water a couple of times a day.
        \n\n\<b>Choosing the Right Food:</b>
        \n\n\t\tThe fish food section at the pet store can be overwhelming to a novice owner. First, learn more about your fish species, starting with whether the species are meat-eaters (carnivores) or vegetation eaters (herbivores). From there, options to choose from include:
        \n\n\t <b>•	Dry Food: </b>When you think of fish food, you think of flakes. That\'s the most common option for feeding a tankful of fish, but dry fish food also comes in granules and pellets, sinking, and floating varieties, as well as options for specific species. Dry fish food can be lower in fiber, but adding vegetable foods to the diet will help reduce the risk of swim bladder disorders and bloating for vegetarian species. Pet stores may also sell sheets of dried spirulina or nori algae, which are great for herbivorous fish to nibble on.
        \n\n\t <b>•	Frozen Food:</b> Some fish will enjoy frozen food, such as shrimp, bloodworms, plankton, prawn, krill, or mussels. Pet stores often also sell frozen spirulina cubes for feeding herbivores.
        \n\n\t<b>•	Freeze Dried: </b>Tubifex worms and Mysis shrimp or other foods can be found as freeze-dried cubes. These are very nutritious and great for carnivorous fish.
        \n\n\t<b>•	Live Food: </b>Options include live brine or ghost shrimp, feeder fish (for larger carnivorous fish), crickets, and worms.
        \n\n\t<b>•	Greens:</b> If your fish are the type to munch on aquarium plants, such as anacharis, give them greens as well. Options include lettuce, cucumber, zucchini, and spinach. Clip the greens to the side of the tank or fasten them in place near the substrate, but remove or replace the uneaten vegetables within 24 hours. Fish such as plecostomus love to eat fresh greens.
        \n\n The biology of different fish means they often need different food. Therefore, if you have a variety of fish in your aquarium, use a combination of food—such as floating foods, slow-sinking foods, and rapidly sinking foods—to ensure they\'re getting the nutrition they need.
        \n\n<b>How much to feed:</b>
        \n\nFish owners are more likely to overfeed their fish than underfeed them, which increases the amount of waste in the tank. This is not only the waste left when the fish do not eat all the food but also the waste is excreted from the fish because they\'re eating more than necessary. If you find that ammonia, nitrite, or nitrate levels are going up and the tank seems polluted, you\'re probably overfeeding the fish.
        \n\nAdult fish can be fed once a day, around the same time, though you can feed them multiple times a day if you\'re giving them a smaller amount each feeding. Young fish may need three or four feedings a day. Herbivores typically don\'t have large stomachs to hold a lot of food, as in nature they would nibble on algae and plants throughout the day. They can be fed more frequently than carnivores, or given live greens that they can snack on throughout the day. Follow the rule of thumb that you should feed the fish only what they will eat in five minutes. If there is food left after that time (except for the fresh greens), you are feeding too much. One exception is for fish that are nocturnal (night time) feeders, where you should put the food in the aquarium in the evening before turning off the lights, and let the fish eat overnight.
        \n\nDon\'t take the size of the aquarium as an indication of how much food is needed. Five fish in a large aquarium need the same amount of food as five fish in a smaller aquarium—just spread it out across the aquarium so everyone can get to it easily.

    </string>
    <string name="rabbbit_food">"Like other animals, rabbits like to eat a variety of fun foods. Regular nutritious and balanced diet helps to keep your favorite rabbit healthy. Take a look at what foods should be on your rabbit\'s food list.
        \n\n<b>Fresh hay:</b>
        \nHay is a very important food for rabbits. It is very important to have it in the daily food list. Older rabbits can be fed grass, oat straw, Timothy Hay. And baby rabbits should be fed Alfalfa. Alfalfa should not be given to adult rabbits due to high protein and sugar. Straw provides the rabbit with the essential fiber needed for good digestive health and it helps to keep a rabbit\’s teeth constantly growing down.
        \n\n<b>Vegetables:</b> \n Vegetables are a varied asset that should be a part of your rabbit\'s daily diet. Always choose fresh and pesticide-free vegetables. Vegetables should be washed well before feeding. Indoor decorative herbs can often be toxic to them.
        Vegetables that should be on the food list –
        \n\tBroccoli leaves- ব্রোকলি পাতা
        \n\tCarrot tops-গাজর একাংশ
        \n\tDill -শুলফা Kale -পাতা কপি
        \n\tLettuce – লেটুস
        \n\tMint/Basil- পুদিনা
        \n\tMustard greens- সরিষা সবুজ শাক
        \n\tParsley- পার্সলে
        \n\tWater cress- জল শাক
        \n\n<b>Water:</b> \n Always keep water for your rabbit. Always keep water in a hanging water bowl or bowl. On hot days you can leave an ice cube in the rabbit water container. If your rabbit does not drink enough water, let it eat wet vegetables.
        \n\n<b>Pellets:</b> \n Rabbit pellets of different brands are available in pet shops. These foods, which are rich in adequate fiber and protein, are very popular with rabbits.
        \n\n<b>Treat:</b> \n You can treat your rabbit occasionally to make it happy, but you have to pay attention to your health. Bread, pasta, salty biscuits, cookies, chips, or cereals should not be fed because they are high in sugar. Never give chocolate, it is toxic to rabbits. The best way to treat is to feed the fruit. But you have to give less amount to have more sugar. Fruits that can be given are- Strawberries, Raspberries, Bananas, Pineapple, Apples (no seeds).     "</string>
    <string name="fish_medicine_header">"Tropical fish medicine is used to treat tropical fish diseases. Tropical fish diseases can be caused by bacteria, fungus or by parasites. Commonly seen tropical fish diseases are Septicemia, Cotton Disease, Dropsy, Fin Rot, Ich, Swim bladder Infection, Pop Eye, Hole in the Head etc. Tropical fish medicine includes Antibiotics, Anti-fungals, Anti-parasitics.

    </string>
    <string name="medicine_fish_1">Praziquantel is known to be one of the safest most effective pond fish medications available for treating a vast array of external and internal parasites. It will not stress pond fish, damage filtration systems, or negatively affect the balance of your pond. One of the biggest advantages in large ponds is that water changes are not necessary and it only takes one treatment.  \n<b>How much:</b> 5 ml treats 25 gallons.  \n<b> How often:</b> One dose per treatment, repeat after 7 days if necessary. \n<b> How to: </b> Dilute liquid treatment in 1 gallon of pond water. Distribute evenly around the pond or add to an area with good circulation.</string>
    <string name="medicine_fish_2">Microbe-Lift Lice  Anchor Worm is the most effective treatment for diseases of fish caused by lice and anchor worms. When used as directed, it will not harm biological filtration and may be used on scaleless fish. Can be used in any water temperatures above 40º F. Should be stored in the original container above 40ºF and under 100ºF. Do not store in direct sunlight and do not allow to freeze.

    This product is intended for use with all ornamental pond fish. Not for use with fish or aquatic invertebrates intended for human consumption. Not for human or veterinary use.
    </string>
    <string name="medicine_fish_3">
        Microbe-Lift BSDT is the preeminent broad spectrum malachite green and formalin treatment. The only malachite green and formalin treatment that can be used in water temperatures as low as 50°F, thus allowing treatment in early Spring and late Fall.

Malachite green and formalin are two drugs that are more effective and less toxic in combination than when used individually. This is the definition of synergism. What makes Microbe-Lift BSDT the preeminent product in this field is the fact that it is formulated with malachite green chloride, instead of the more toxic oxalate salt. As with any malachite green and formalin treatment, do NOT use with other medications.
    </string>
    <string name="medicine_fish_4">
A unique, natural parasite repellant. Proven to work against bacterial dropsy, fungus and ulcers in fish. Expels pathogens from fish and stimulates its immune system response. Can speed up damaged tissue regeneration.

\n\nSabbactisun is made with plant and herbal extracts making it environmentally friendly. Supports immune system, driving off the excess parasites. Product is harmless to all nitrifying filter bacteria and aquatic plants

\n\n<b>Benefits:</b>
\n\n\t100% natural plant and herbal product
\n\tCompletely safe to use
\n\tNontoxic to animals and plants
\n\tProduct can be used during feeding
\n\tDoes not adversely affect either nitrifying filter bacteria or beneficial bacteria additives
\n\tNo significant reduction in the level of dissolved oxygen in the water
\n\tFully Biodegradable
\n\tSabbactisun and Parazoryne can be used 12 hours apart
    </string>

    <string name="medicine_fish_5">
Aqua MedZyme permanently reduces ALL strains of deadly ulcer causing Aeromonas, Pseudomonas in your pond by starving them to death. These deadly bacteria live in every koi fish pond, causing life threatening bacterial infections such as ulcers, fin rot, tail rot and more. Attacking koi when they are stressed, causing thousands of fish deaths each year. Aqua MedZyme contains 760,000,000 yes, seven hundred and sixty million hungry beneficial bacteria per ml that eat the same food as Aeromonas, Pseudomonas, which starves them to levels so low they can not harm your fish.

\n\t1.Treats pond water as low as 40°F
\n\t2.Great for early spring and fall treatments
\n\t3.Does NOT contain chemicals, antibiotics or medications
\n\t4.100% natural - safe for filters, plants, pets and wildlife
\n\t5.Formula has been tested extensively in koi ponds, commercial aquaculture applications, private veterinary laboratories and University Studies    </string>
    <string name="fish_medicine">
        "\tCelecoxib Oral Suspension.
        \n\tCelecoxib Oral Suspension.
        \n\tFluconazole Oral Suspension.
        \n\tAmikacin Injection Solution.
        \n\tMetronidazole Oral Suspension.
        \n\tCalcium Glubionate Oral Syrup.
        \n\tAmphotericin B Oral Suspension.
        \n\tCiprofloxacin Oral Oil Suspension.  "</string>
    <string name="rabbit_medicine">
        	Furosemide Oral Suspension.
\n\n	Amikacin Injection Solution.
\n\n	Metronidazole Oral Suspension.
\n\n	Buprenorphine Injection Solution.
\n\n	Albendazole Capsule.
\n\n	Meloxicam Oral Suspension.
\n\n	Meloxicam Oral Suspension.
\n\n	Doxycycline Oral Suspension.

 "</string>
    <string name="peraid">"<b>Your Kit Should Contain</b>
        \n\n\t•\tAbsorbent gauze pads
        \n\t•\tAdhesive tape
        \n\t•\tCotton balls or swabs
        \n\t•\tFresh 3% hydrogen peroxide to induce vomiting (always check with veterinarian or animal poison control expert before giving to your pet)
        \n\t•\tIce pack
        \n\t•\tDisposable gloves
        \n\t•\tScissors with blunt end
        \n\t•\tTweezers
        \n\t•\tOral syringe or turkey baster
        \n\t•\tLiquid dishwashing detergent (for bathing)
        \n\t•\tTowels
        \n\t•\tSmall flashlight
        \n\t•\tAlcohol wipes
        \n\t•\tStyptic powder
        \n\t•\tSaline eye solution
        \n\t•\tArtificial tear gel
        \n\t•\tPhone number, clinic name, address of your veterinarian as well as local veterinary emergency clinics.   Make sure to check your pack every few months to make sure nothing has expired or needs to be replaced. And of course keep your kit out of the reach of children. "</string>
    <string name="peraid2">"<b>Here’s What You’ll Need:</b>
        \n\n\t•\tPhone number, clinic name, address of your veterinarian PLUS contact info for local veterinary emergency clinics
        \n\t•\tAbsorbent gauze pads
        \n\t•\tAdhesive tape
        \n\t•\tCotton balls or swabs
        \n\t•\tFresh 3% hydrogen peroxide to induce vomiting (always check with veterinarian or animal poison control expert before giving to your pet)
        \n\t•\tIce pack
        \n\t•\tDisposable gloves
        \n\t•\tScissors with blunt end PLUS tweezers
        \n\t•\tOver-the-counter antibiotic ointment
        \n\t•\tLiquid dishwashing detergent for bathing PLUS towels
        \n\t•\tSmall flashlight
        \n\t•\tOral syringe or kitchen baster
        \n\t•\tAlcohol wipes
        \n\t•\tStyptic powder
        \n\t•\tSaline eye solution

</string>
    <string name="antrax">
        Anthrax, a highly infectious and fatal disease of cattle, is caused by a relatively large spore-forming rectangular shaped bacterium called Bacillus anthraces. Anthrax causes acute mortality in ruminants. The bacteria produce extremely potent toxins which are responsible for the ill effects, causing a high mortality rate. Signs of the illness usually appear 3 to 7 days after the spores are swallowed or inhaled. Once signs begin in animals, they usually die within two days.

Hoofed animals, such as deer, cattle, goats, and sheep, are the main animals affected by this disease. They usually get the disease by swallowing anthrax spores while grazing on pasture contaminated (made impure) with anthrax spores. Inhaling (breathing in) the spores, which are odorless, colorless, and tasteless, may also cause infection in animals and people.

\n\n<b>Symptoms:</b>
\n\n\t	Sudden death (often within 2 or 3 hours of being apparently normal) is by far the most common sign;
\n\t	Very occasionally some animals may show trembling, a high temperature
\n\t	Difficulty breathing, collapse and convulsions before death. This usually occurs over a period of 24 hours;
\n\t	After death blood, may not clot, resulting in a small amount of bloody discharge from the nose, mouth and other openings
Treatment and control
\n\t	Due to the acute nature of the disease resulting in sudden death, treatment is usually not possible in animals even though Anthrax bacilli are clines. Treatment is of use in cases showing sub-acute form of the disease.
\n\t	In most cases, early treatment can cure anthrax. The cutaneous (skin) form of anthrax can be treated with common antibiotics.




\n\n<b>Preventive measures:</b>
\n\t	Regular annual vaccination of animals in endemic areas will prevent the disease from occurring.
\n\t	Vaccination may be carried out at least a month prior to expected disease occurrence in endemic areas.
\n\t	Never open a carcass of an animal suspected to have died from anthrax.
\nContact a veterinarian immediately if the following symptoms are seen and seek advice on control measures to be adopted.
\n\t	Fever (106-108°F), loss of appetite, depression and dullness
\n\t	Suspended rumination3. Rapid pulse and heart rates
\n\t	Difficult breathing (dyspnea)
\n\t	Lameness in affected leg
\n\t	Crepitation swelling over hip, back and shoulder
\n\t	Swelling is hot and painful in early stages whereas cold and painless inter.
\n\t	Recumbence (prostration) followed by death within 12-48 hrs.

    </string>
    <string name="medicinecat"><b>Antibiotics:</b> these are drugs that kill microbes, such as bacteria and yeast, and are used to treat infections.
        They don’t kill viruses, but they are sometimes prescribed to treat secondary bacterial infections that can occur when an animal is ill from a viral infection.
        Examples in dogs and cats include penicillin, trimethoprim-sulfa, cephalexin and enrofloxacin.
        \n\n<b>Non-steroidal anti-inflammatories:</b> these common drugs reduce swelling, inflammation, pain and lameness. Examples include carprofen, deracoxib, firocoxib,
        and meloxicam. Opioid pain relievers: these medications are generally derived from morphine and can be potent pain relievers. Examples include oxycodone,
        hydromorphone, butorphanol, meperidine and fentanyl. Most of these drugs are controlled substances because of their addictive potential.
        \n\n<b>Steroids: </b>steroids have many different uses. They can be potent anti-inflammatories and are frequently used to reduce allergic and anaphylactic reactions.
        They are also used at high doses to suppress the immune system.  Examples include prednisone, prednisolone and dexamethasone.
        \n\n<b>Antiparasitics: </b>these products are intended to prevent, repel or kill internal or external parasites such as intestinal worms, intestinal protozoans
        (Giardia, etc.), heartworms, fleas and ticks.
        \n\n<b>Behavior-modifying drugs and sedatives: </b>these drugs are used to quiet anxious pets or help in reducing anxiety associated with various behavioral issues in pets, prepare pets for anesthesia, and to reduce pet movement during delicate procedures.
        Examples include diazepam, xylazine, acepromazine and midazolam.
        \n\n<b>Hormones and other medications used to treat specific conditions:</b> Examples include insulin used for diabetes treatment, methimazole or levothyroxine for abnormal thyroid hormone levels, and heart medications such as atenolol, digoxin, and pimobendan.
        \n\n<b>Chemotherapeutics:</b> these drugs are used to treat tumors and cancer. Examples include cisplatin, vincristine, doxorubicin and cyclophosphamide. "</string>
    <string name="medicinecat2">Drugs act in very different ways, and sometimes these different mechanisms can result in one drug interfering with another drug in some
        way. In addition, the body’s method of eliminating one drug can affect another medication by changing its rate of elimination from the body. \n\nTwo drugs might
        have an additive effect, where the result produced is more than expected. This could be beneficial, but it could also be harmful. \n\nOne drug might speed up or
        slow down the body’s metabolism or elimination of another drug, which could result in toxicity, organ damage, or ineffective treatment. One drug might prevent
        another medication from being effective by interfering with how it acts in the body.\n\n Always tell your veterinarian the medications, including any over-the-counter
        medications and supplements (including vitamins and any holistic or homeopathic products), that you are giving your pet. Write down how often, how much, and how you
        give them and share this list with your veterinarian. "</string>
    <string name="medicinecat3">\nIn general, medication choices involve weighing the advantages of the medication (stopping infection, reducing pain, etc.) against the potential risks, and taking measures to reduce side effects as much as possible. These preventive measures vary with the medication but can include keeping the drug dose and frequency as low as possible (but still effective); giving the drug for the shortest time needed; and giving the medication on a full or empty stomach.  \n\nWeighing the advantages and risks is an important process your veterinarian does, in part because the very mechanisms that make drugs effective for treating conditions can also cause unwanted effects. For example, non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs) reduce the production of prostaglandins, many of which increase inflammation, pain and swelling. However, there are “good” prostaglandins in our bodies (and our pet’s bodies) that actually help protect us; an example is Prostaglandin E, which helps prevent our stomach from developing ulcers. Taking a NSAID reduces pain, swelling and lameness after an injury, but long-term use of NSAIDs can lead to stomach problems because of their effect in reducing Prostaglandin E. In addition, long-term use of NSAIDs can negatively affect prostaglandins in the kidneys, resulting in changes in blood flow within the kidney that can lead to kidney damage. This is why it’s so important to read any information your veterinarian gives you about the product, and to call your veterinarian if you suspect adverse events from any drug your dog or cat is taking. "</string>
    <string name="medicinedog2">"<b>Medicines for Dog</b>\n
        \tAntibiotics. Antibiotics such as Metronidazole and Doxycycline are frequently prescribed to dogs fighting bacterial infections. \n\tAntiparasitics \n\tAntifungals \n\tSteroids \n\tPain Relievers "</string>
    <string-array name="pet">
        <item>Rabbit</item>
        <item>Cat</item>
        <item>Dog</item>
        <item>Bird</item>
        <item>Fish</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sex">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>