<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animal Lover</string>
    <string name="new_user_sign_here">New User?    <u>SIGN UP</u> Here</string>
    <string name="already_registered_login_here">Already Registered? <u>Login here</u> </string>
    <string name="doing_great_work">Help the Animals\n If you love them</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">This guide will help you setup\n everything about Animal Lover</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="typesfoodcat">
         1.Dry food diet\n
        2.Wet food diet\n
        3.Renal diet\n
        4.Gastrointestinal health diets\n
        5.High energy diet\n

    </string>
    <string name="typesmedicinecat">
         1.Fluids for Cats\n
        2.Digestive Disorder Products for Cats\n
        3.Hormone Replacement or Inhibition for Cats\n
        4.Heart and Blood Pressure Drugs for Cats\n
        5.Bronchodilators for Cats\n

    </string>
    <string name="foodlistcat">
          1.Salmon\n
         2.Trout\n
         3.Herring\n
         4.Mackerel\n
         5.Tuna\n
         6.Whitefish\n
         7.Chicken\n
         8.Turkey\n
         9.Pheasant\n
         10.Beef\n

    </string>
    <string name="typesfoodbird">
        #1: Bird seed mixtures\n
        #2: Bird cake and food bars\n
        #3: Live foods and other insect foods\n
        #4: Breed your own mealworms\n
        #5: Household scraps for birds
    </string>

    <string name="typesfooddog">
        #1: Kibble/Dry\n
        #2: Canned\n
        #3: Semi-Moist\n
        #4: Home Cooked\n
        #5: Raw
    </string>
    <string name="foodlistdog">
       Top Food Names for Female Dogs:\n
        1.Ginger\n
        2.Pepper\n
        3.Cookie
        4.Cinnamon
        5.Snickers\n\n
        Top Food Names for Male Dogs\n
        1.Pickles\n
        2.Peanut\n
        3.Pepper\n
        4.Brownie\n
        5.Chip\n
    </string>
    <string name="when_your_pet_has_a_medical_condition_your_veterinarian_might_prescribe_one_or_more_medications_intended_to_manage_treat_or_cure_the_problem_although_there_are_some_veterinary_specific_drugs_many_of_the_drugs_used_in_veterinary_medicine_are_the_same_as_those_used_in_people_ata_medicine_er_vitor_deoa_lagbe_jeta_already_medicines_doc_file_deoa_ache_amra_kono_vabe_daye_thakbo_na_jekono_kisu_medicine_use_korar_agee_doctor_or_prescribe_hoa_lagbe">When your pet has a medical condition, your veterinarian might prescribe one or more medications intended to manage, treat or cure the problem. Although there are some veterinary-specific drugs, many of the drugs used in veterinary medicine are the same as those used in people. ata medicine er vitor deoa lagbe jeta already medicines doc file deoa ache ... amra kono vabe daye thakbo na . jekono kisu medicine use korar agee doctor or prescribe hoa lagbe</string>
    <string name="warning"><b>Warning- </b>As with any fresh food you offer your bird, remove and discard any leftovers a
        couple of hours after serving. This prevents bacteria growth inside of your pet’s cage. Take it easy on the grapes,
        however. They contain a lot of sugar. </string>
    <string name="warning2">
        <b>Warning- </b>Remember to never serve raw beans to your companion bird as they can be toxic unless cooked.
    </string>
    <string name="dog_food">"Dogs are usually carnivorous and eat almost all types of food. But wild dogs eat the flesh, bones, various organs and digested plants of other animals that prey on themselves. Although dogs are carnivores, they consume very small amounts of vegetable food for prey digestion.
        \n\nFeed good quality dry food or canned food according to the age and weight of the dog. These processed foods contain the right amount of nutrients. Dog food of different brands and flavors is available in the market and in different online shops. However, look at the expiration date on the food packet and try to feed premium food.
        \n\n\t\t •\tFeed Natural Foods. Such as: meat (beef, chicken, sheep, etc.), eggs, bones and various vegetable foods.
        \n\n\t •\tIf your dog has a problem with his teeth or gums, do not let him eat the bones. Bone can cause various gum and dental diseases. Playing too much bone can cause constipation and the bone should be large so that the whole bone does not get into the mouth.
        \n\n\t •\tOccasionally canned fish such as sardines, tuna, salmon, etc. can be fed as a treat  •\tOccasionally a small amount of boiled vegetables such as sweet pumpkin, carrot, broccoli, etc. can be fed.  •\tDogs can be fed rice or pasta mixed with boiled meat (without spices, onions, garlic).
        \n\n\t•\tLet the dog eat grass which acts as a vegetable substitute and helps digestion. Beware of chemical and poisonous plants.
        \n\n\t•\tThe amount of food depends on the size, breed, age, weight, exercise, etc. of the dog. However, it should be noted that extra food or very small amount of food should not be fed.
        \n\n\t•\tAdult dogs need to be fed twice a day. Exercise and walking should not be done just before and just after eating.
        \n\n\t•\tSome foods that should not be fed to dogs (toxic to dogs) are onions, garlic, chocolate, coffee and caffeine, avocado fruit, raw flour, yeast, grapes, raisins, nuts, fruit seeds or grains such as mango flour, avocado fruit Grains, raw tomatoes, mushrooms, daily fish, small bones, Xylitol (used instead of sugar in various foods), chewing gum, toothpaste, etc. "
    </string>
    <string name="fish_food">"What you feed your fish and how much you feed them—is an important part of providing a healthy environment for them. There's much more to offering the proper diet for a fish than just sprinkling a few flakes on top of the water a couple of times a day.
        \n\n\<b>Choosing the Right Food:</b>
        \n\n\t\tThe fish food section at the pet store can be overwhelming to a novice owner. First, learn more about your fish species, starting with whether the species are meat-eaters (carnivores) or vegetation eaters (herbivores). From there, options to choose from include:
        \n\n\t <b>•	Dry Food: </b>When you think of fish food, you think of flakes. That\'s the most common option for feeding a tankful of fish, but dry fish food also comes in granules and pellets, sinking, and floating varieties, as well as options for specific species. Dry fish food can be lower in fiber, but adding vegetable foods to the diet will help reduce the risk of swim bladder disorders and bloating for vegetarian species. Pet stores may also sell sheets of dried spirulina or nori algae, which are great for herbivorous fish to nibble on.
        \n\n\t <b>•	Frozen Food:</b> Some fish will enjoy frozen food, such as shrimp, bloodworms, plankton, prawn, krill, or mussels. Pet stores often also sell frozen spirulina cubes for feeding herbivores.
        \n\n\t<b>•	Freeze Dried: </b>Tubifex worms and Mysis shrimp or other foods can be found as freeze-dried cubes. These are very nutritious and great for carnivorous fish.
        \n\n\t<b>•	Live Food: </b>Options include live brine or ghost shrimp, feeder fish (for larger carnivorous fish), crickets, and worms.
        \n\n\t<b>•	Greens:</b> If your fish are the type to munch on aquarium plants, such as anacharis, give them greens as well. Options include lettuce, cucumber, zucchini, and spinach. Clip the greens to the side of the tank or fasten them in place near the substrate, but remove or replace the uneaten vegetables within 24 hours. Fish such as plecostomus love to eat fresh greens.
        \n\n The biology of different fish means they often need different food. Therefore, if you have a variety of fish in your aquarium, use a combination of food—such as floating foods, slow-sinking foods, and rapidly sinking foods—to ensure they\'re getting the nutrition they need.
        \n\n<b>How much to feed:</b>
        \n\nFish owners are more likely to overfeed their fish than underfeed them, which increases the amount of waste in the tank. This is not only the waste left when the fish do not eat all the food but also the waste is excreted from the fish because they\'re eating more than necessary. If you find that ammonia, nitrite, or nitrate levels are going up and the tank seems polluted, you\'re probably overfeeding the fish.
        \n\nAdult fish can be fed once a day, around the same time, though you can feed them multiple times a day if you\'re giving them a smaller amount each feeding. Young fish may need three or four feedings a day. Herbivores typically don\'t have large stomachs to hold a lot of food, as in nature they would nibble on algae and plants throughout the day. They can be fed more frequently than carnivores, or given live greens that they can snack on throughout the day. Follow the rule of thumb that you should feed the fish only what they will eat in five minutes. If there is food left after that time (except for the fresh greens), you are feeding too much. One exception is for fish that are nocturnal (night time) feeders, where you should put the food in the aquarium in the evening before turning off the lights, and let the fish eat overnight.
        \n\nDon\'t take the size of the aquarium as an indication of how much food is needed. Five fish in a large aquarium need the same amount of food as five fish in a smaller aquarium—just spread it out across the aquarium so everyone can get to it easily.

    </string>
    <string name="rabbbit_food">"Like other animals, rabbits like to eat a variety of fun foods. Regular nutritious and balanced diet helps to keep your favorite rabbit healthy. Take a look at what foods should be on your rabbit\'s food list.
        \n\n<b>Fresh hay:</b>
        \nHay is a very important food for rabbits. It is very important to have it in the daily food list. Older rabbits can be fed grass, oat straw, Timothy Hay. And baby rabbits should be fed Alfalfa. Alfalfa should not be given to adult rabbits due to high protein and sugar. Straw provides the rabbit with the essential fiber needed for good digestive health and it helps to keep a rabbit\’s teeth constantly growing down.
        \n\n<b>Vegetables:</b> \n Vegetables are a varied asset that should be a part of your rabbit\'s daily diet. Always choose fresh and pesticide-free vegetables. Vegetables should be washed well before feeding. Indoor decorative herbs can often be toxic to them.
        Vegetables that should be on the food list –
        \n\tBroccoli leaves- ব্রোকলি পাতা
        \n\tCarrot tops-গাজর একাংশ
        \n\tDill -শুলফা Kale -পাতা কপি
        \n\tLettuce – লেটুস
        \n\tMint/Basil- পুদিনা
        \n\tMustard greens- সরিষা সবুজ শাক
        \n\tParsley- পার্সলে
        \n\tWater cress- জল শাক
        \n\n<b>Water:</b> \n Always keep water for your rabbit. Always keep water in a hanging water bowl or bowl. On hot days you can leave an ice cube in the rabbit water container. If your rabbit does not drink enough water, let it eat wet vegetables.
        \n\n<b>Pellets:</b> \n Rabbit pellets of different brands are available in pet shops. These foods, which are rich in adequate fiber and protein, are very popular with rabbits.
        \n\n<b>Treat:</b> \n You can treat your rabbit occasionally to make it happy, but you have to pay attention to your health. Bread, pasta, salty biscuits, cookies, chips, or cereals should not be fed because they are high in sugar. Never give chocolate, it is toxic to rabbits. The best way to treat is to feed the fruit. But you have to give less amount to have more sugar. Fruits that can be given are- Strawberries, Raspberries, Bananas, Pineapple, Apples (no seeds).     "</string>

    <string-array name="pet">
        <item>Rabbit</item>
        <item>Cat</item>
        <item>Dog</item>
        <item>Bird</item>
        <item>Fish</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sex">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>